Wolff, Sidney A. Additional Arbitration Files 5637
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Social Security - Union Carbide (Box 8)
  - Social Security Administration, Department of Health Education and Welfare and the New York-New Jersey Council of District Office Locals of the American Federal Government Employees (1 issue), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Issue: Employee Rights - failure to wear a necktie, working conditions, discrimination Includes Decision and Recommendations from the Labor Relations Reporter, general arbitration, arbitration bill, arbitration report and fee statement, award, manuscript notes, opening statement (union), general correspondence, supporting documentation, clippings, Agreement (1971), post hearing brief (union), comments and observations on Union post-hearing brief
  - South Central Bell Company and CWA, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company and the Communication Workers of America - failure to pay: pay differentials, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    general correspondence, award, arbitration bill, manuscript notes, Agreement Interpretation (1971), Company brief, Union brief
  - Space Age Talent and American Guild of Variety Artists and HY Einhorn - salary for cancelled dates (Performance dates), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    general correspondence, award, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - Sperry Rand Corporation, Univac Division and the IAM Local 157 - vacation entitlement, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    award, general correspondence, manuscript notes, arbitration bill, company brief, Agreement, supporting documentation, Union reply brief
  - Sperry Rand Corporation and the IAM - violation of seniority rights, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    general correspondence, award and issue, manuscript notes, article by Thomas J. McDermott "Types of seniority Provisions and the Measurement of Ability" - 1970 (printed in the Arbitration Journal #2), supporting documentation
  - Spring Valley, Village of and the Policemen's Benevolent Association - Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    includes: terms of agreement, recognition, work day and work week, overtime, vacations, holiday and personal leave, health insurance, life insurance, sick leave, grievance and arbitration, discharge and discipline, uniform allowance, college courses, rights of employees, salaries, night shift, differential, longevity, duration Also includes: general correspondence, award, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, salaries of village policemen in New York (1974), Agreement (1968), Village of Spring Valley Budget (1975-1976), award, Employer's Submission, Fact-Finder Report, Affidavit, arbitration bill, past cases (City of Syracuse and the Syracuse Police Benevolent Association 1975, Opinion and award of arbitration), Report - A survey of Crime in Spring Valley and recommendations for Action--submitted by the Mid-Hudson Crime Control Planning Board for the Board of Trustees, village of Spring Valley, clippings
  - [] and SMS versus Oil, Chemical, and atomic Workers Local 9-138, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    correspondence only First word too faded to read
  - Standard Brands Incorporated and the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 892, Chauffeurs and Warehousemen of America - creation of jobs in violation of the present contract, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    award, manuscript notes, Agreement (1970), supporting documentation, company post hearing brief, post awards (same company and Union), opinion and award, arbitration bill
  - Standard Motor Products and the UAW local 9-A - discharge, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    award and opinion; general correspondence, arbitration bill, report of panel arbitration, manuscript notes
  - Stanley Tools, Eagle Square Plant and the Upholsterers' International Union local 645 - Machinists doing work outside of job description, 1975- 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    general correspondence, issue and award, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, union brief, manuscript notes, company brief
  - Stanley Tools, Eagle Square Plant and the Upholsterers' International Union - change in health plan, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    award and issue, arbitration bill, Agreement (1972), copy of Employees Insurance Plant (1972), manuscript note, Agreement (1972)
  - Stanley Works and Stanley Tools Division and IAM Local 1249 - transfer in lieu of layoff but to a lower step rate in the established rate range for such classification, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    general correspondence, issue and award, manuscript notes, company brief, supporting documentation
  - Stauffer Chemical Company versus United Rubber Workers Local 584, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Stewart-Warner Corporation versus IUE Local 229, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Stotter, H.J. Incorporated and the District 65 wholesale, Retail, Office and Processing Union - discharge, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    general correspondence, manuscript notes, memorandum opinion, supporting documentation, union memorandum, Employer's post hearing memorandum, manuscript notes
  - Suflex Corporation and the Textile Workers Union of America - Transfer, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    general correspondence, memorandum
  - Supermarkets General Corporation and District 1199, Drug and Hospital Union and the Supermarkets General Corporation - discharge, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    manuscript notes, arbitration bill, issues and award, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - Tappan Company versus UAW Local 1068, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Teletyne Wirz versus local 12754, International Union District 50, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Telemet Company and District 65, RWDSU - discharge, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    general correspondence, award, arbitration bill, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - Tenneco Chemicals, Incorporated and the United Steelworkers of America - overtime, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    arbitration bill, FMCS award, general correspondence, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - Texaco versus Oil Chemical Workers Local 8-638, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Ton-Tex versus IGT Local 999, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    correspondence only Unsure about "Ton-Tex," entry is faded
  - Torrington Company and the UAW - disciplinary suspension, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    arbitration bill, award, general correspondence, manuscript notes, company brief, transcripts, supporting documentation
  - Torrington Company and the UAW Local 1645 - wage rates, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    general correspondence, transcripts, opinion and award, company brief, supporting documentation
  - Trumbull Police Local and the Connecticut Council of Police Union - seniority, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    general correspondence, motion for production
  - Ungerer and Company and the Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local P-653 - work assignment, management rights and overtime pay, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    general correspondence, award, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, arbitration report and fee statement
  - Union Camp Corporation and the United Paperworkers International Union Local 1692 - vacation pay, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    general correspondence, issue and award, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - Union Camp Corporation and the United Paperworkers International Union Local 15 - Did the Company violate the agreement by not calling in the grievant to work the first shift when his counterpart on first shift failed to report for work?, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    general correspondence, arbitration report and fee statement, award, arbitration bill, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - Union Carbide Corporation, Chemicals and Plastics Division, and the Chemical Crafts Union - contract interpretation, scheduling of work, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    general correspondence, arbitration report and fee schedule, manuscript notes, issue and award, company brief, supporting documentation
- Union News - Westinghouse Local 1035 (Box 9)
  - Union News Company and the Retail Drug, Cigar, Soda and Luncheonette Employees Union Local 906 - back pay, payments to welfare and pension funds and shortage disputes, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    award, manuscript notes, general correspondence, report of arbitration panel, supporting documentation, reply memo of the American News Company
  - United Broadcasting of New York, Incorporated and the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists - Station WBNX, amounts of payments to the AFTRA Pension and Welfare Funds, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - United Parcel Service and the IAM District 15 - discharge, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    award, manuscript notes, oath of arbitration, report of panel arbitrators, general correspondence, supporting documentation
  - United Transformer Company and the International Union of Electrical and Radio and Machine Workers Local 431 - sub-contracting, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    general correspondence, manuscript notes, agreement (1970), supporting documentation, pre-hearing memo on behalf of the employer
  - Unity Funeral Homes, Incorporated and the Service Employees International Union Local 100 - assignment of bargaining unit work to managers and assistant managers at all locations, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    general correspondence, notice of intention to arbitrate
  - Universal Carloading and Distributing Company, Incorporated and the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees - discharge, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    general correspondence, arbitration bills, arbitration report and fee statement, award, manuscript notes, union post-hearing brief, supporting documentation, employer's brief, affidavits, union's opening statement
  - Universal Carloading and Distributing Company, Incorporated and the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees - discharge, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    general correspondence, arbitration bills, arbitration report and fee statement, award, manuscript notes, union post hearing brief, supporting documentation, employer's brief, affidavits, union's opening statement
  - V.A.W. and the United Steel Workers of America District 4 - seniority, sick pay eligibility grievance, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    general correspondence, award, opinion, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - Victory Graphic Arts versus United Paperworkers International Union Local 292, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - WBEN Incorporated versus NABET, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Wells Fargo Alarm Services and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 3 - discharge, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    general correspondence, award, opinion, union brief, employer's post-hearing brief, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - West Chemical Products, Incorporated and the District 50, Allied Technical Workers of the United States and Canada - upgrading of classifications, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    award, manuscript notes, arbitration memorandum (company), supporting documentation, general correspondence
  - Western Electric Company and the Communication Equipment Workers Incorporated - job classifications, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    general correspondence, manuscript notes, award, union reply brief, company reply brief
  - Western Electric Company versus Communication Equipment Workers - job classification, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    post- hearing memorandum (company), 3 volume transcripts, supporting documentation, union post hearing brief, general correspondence
  - Western Electric Company and the Communication Workers of America, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Western Electric Company and the Communication Workers of America - suspension, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    manuscript notes, general correspondence, transcripts, company post-hearing brief, supporting documentation, award, union brief
  - Western Electric Company, Connecticut Service Center and the Communication Workers of America Local 1295, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, general correspondence, union brief, company post-hearing brief, transcript
  - Western Electric Company versus Point Breeze Salaried Employees Association, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Westinghouse Local 130 - Wolf (plus notebooks on Western Electric) (Box 10)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation and IUE Local 130 - refusal to discharge for his failure to maintain union membership, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    general correspondence, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, post-hearing brief on delay of the company, transcripts, union post-hearing brief
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation versus IUE local 130, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation versus IUE Local 617 - discipline, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    award, arbitration proceedings, post-hearing brief on behalf of the union, manuscript notes, general correspondence
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation versus IUE Local 711, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation versus IUE Local 711, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation versus IUE Local 746, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation versus IUE Local 449, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation versus IUE Local 449, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation versus IUE Local 449, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation versus IUE Local 449, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation versus IUE Local 449, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation and the International Brotherhood of electrical Workers Local 1035 - suspension, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    general correspondence, award and opinion, transcript, post hearing brief (union and company), manuscript notes
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation and the International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers Local 449 - vacation day (observance of Washington's Birthday, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    general correspondence, opinion and award, post hearing brief on behalf of the union, transcript, manuscript notes, post hearing brief on behalf of the company, supporting documentation
  - Westvaco Corporation and the United Paperworkers International Union Local 1831 - overtime pay, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    award, general correspondence, opinion and award, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, company brief
  - Westvaco Corporation versus United Paperworkers International Union Local 1831, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - White Plains Hospital Association versus IUOE Local 30, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Wilson and Company and the Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 1 - holidays which fall on a non-work day, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    manuscript notes, award and opinion, general correspondence, arbitration bill
  - Wilson and Company, and the Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 1 - discharge, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    general correspondence, manuscript notes, award and opinion, arbitration bill
  - Winthrop Laboratories and the International Chemical Workers Local 61 - work assignment, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    arbitration report and fee statement, general correspondence, manuscript notes
  - Wire Workers Manufacturing Association and the Shopmen Local Union #255 - vacation entitlement for employees who were on strike, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    award and opinion, arbitration brief, general correspondence, supporting documentation, manuscript notes, Agreement
  - Wolf Auto Sales and the UAW Local 259 - installation and maintenance by the employees of a closed circuit television, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    opinion and award, manuscript notes, general correspondence, Report of Arbitrator (name cut off)
- Telephone Industry (Box 11)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company versus IBEW Local 827, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - New York Telephone Company and the Communication Workers of America Local 1127 - suspension, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    union memo, transcripts (2 volumes), manuscript notes, company memorandum, general correspondence
  - New York Telephone Company and the Communication Workers of America - discharge, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    transcripts, award and opinion, manuscript notes, general correspondence, union post-hearing brief, company brief
  - New York Telephone Company versus CWA, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - New York Telephone Company versus Telephone traffic Union of New York - claim for compensatory time off, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    opinion and award, arbitration bill, memorandum on behalf of the union, union brief, company brief, manuscript notes, transcripts, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, general correspondence
  - (Pennsylvania) Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and the Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania -title jurisdiction relating to protecting PIC splices under 8-A type closures in non-aerial plant, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    opinion and award, general correspondence, manuscript notes, union opening statement, manuscript notes
  - (Pennsylvania) Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania and the Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania - 6 issues, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Has the company under the PIC Agreement improperly assigned to crafts other than splicers the capping of pic cables where an insulating compound is used in the cap? Job classification, work assignment Does the pic agreement limit the type of terminals or other types of equipment on which crafts other than splicers may perform pic splicing work? Is the replacement of a pic, lead or other cable, with a piece of pic cable "new construction work" under paragraph one of the pic agreement or a "subsequent change" under paragraph 2? Reasonable time period to measure pic work determination of the major pic disagreement includes: general correspondence, manuscript notes, opinion and award
  - Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and the federation of Telephone Workers - 6 issues (continued), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Has the company under the PIC Agreement improperly assigned to crafts other than splicers the capping of pic cables where an insulating compound is used in the cap? Job classification, work assignment Does the pic agreement limit the type of terminals or other types of equipment on which crafts other than splicers may perform pic splicing work? Is the replacement of a pic, lead or other cable, with a piece of pic cable "new construction work" under paragraph one of the pic agreement or a "subsequent change" under paragraph 2? Reasonable time period to measure pic work determination of the major pic disagreement includes: supporting documentation, union brief, company brief (2 volumes), union post-hearing memorandum, general correspondence, arbitration bill, company brief re: fourth PIC arbitration, union brief re: 4th PIC arbitration, opening statement of the company in the 4th PIC case, manuscript notes; transcripts: 4th pic arbitration, exhibits; 4th pic arbitration case (1969), the PIC agreement administration procedures
- Airline Industry (Box 12)
  - British Overseas airway Corporation (BOAC) versus IAM, District Lodge 100, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - British Overseas Airway Corporation versus IAM District 100 - promotion, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    arbitration bill, general correspondence, opinion and award, manuscript notes, union summary brief, supporting documentation, Memorandum of Agreement (1962)
  - British Overseas Airway Corporation and the IAM - discharge, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Agreement (1967), supporting documentation, transcripts, company brief, union summary brief, general correspondence, opinion and award, manuscript notes
  - British Overseas Airway Corporation and the IAM District 100 - suspension, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    opinion and award, manuscript notes, general correspondence
  - British Overseas Airway Corporation and the IAM District 100 - discharge, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, union summary brief, manuscript notes, company brief, supporting documentation, arbitration bill, general correspondence
  - British Overseas Airway Corporation and the IAM District 100 - suspension, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    opinion and award, transcripts (2 volumes), general correspondence, supporting documentation, company reply brief, IAM reply memorandum, IAM memorandum, company brief, manuscript notes
  - Eastern Airlines, Eastern Airlines Pilots System Board of Adjustment and the Air Lines Pilot Association - wage rates, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    transcripts (3 volumes), opinion and award, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, opinion of neutral member, brief, arbitration bill, system crew schedule manual (1961), arbitration bill, union brief, memorandum brief, Agreement (1960), company brief, manuscript notes
  - Eastern Airlines, Eastern Airlines Pilots System Board of Adjustment and the Air Lines Pilot Association, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, JFK versus NAATS, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Lawrence Aviation Industries and the IAM District 15 - assignment and jobs, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lockheed Aircraft Services Company versus IAM Local 1834, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Northwest Airlines Incorporated and Airline Stewards and Stewardesses - discharge, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    opinion and award, transcripts (3 volumes), general correspondence, arbitration bill, supporting documentation, post-hearing memorandum of the company, manuscript notes, union brief
  - Northwest Airlines and Air Line Pilots Association International - crew lounge facilities, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    general correspondence, general correspondence manuscript notes, transcripts
  - Northwest Airlines Pilots Association and the Air Line Pilots Association - pay differentials, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    general correspondence, arbitration bill, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - Northwest Airlines and the Air Lines Pilot Association - pay claims, group grievance, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    general correspondence, opinion and award, manuscript notes, post-hearing memorandum of company, supporting documents, transcripts, Association memorandum brief, Agreement (1969), manuscript notes